[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 11, "question": "Your life is extraordinary, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "life", "is", "extraordinary", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 12, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 29, "question": "But that's the best way, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "that", "'s", "the", "best", "way", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 30, "answer": "URNETT: Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["URNETT", ":", "Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "She didn't really mean it in the most flattering way, didn't she?", "question_tokens": ["She", "did", "n't", "really", "mean", "it", "in", "the", "most", "flattering", "way", ",", "did", "n't", "she", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "VBG", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "No, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "What is it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "Well, right now it's the writing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "right", "now", "it", "'s", "the", "writing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "How do you feel about being described as a living legend?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "being", "described", "as", "a", "living", "legend", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "Old.", "answer_tokens": ["Old", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "You know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "Lifetime achievement.", "answer_tokens": ["Lifetime", "achievement", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "How important was it for you to lead a sort of healthy, active life given that you came from two parents who were both alcoholics, weren't they?", "question_tokens": ["How", "important", "was", "it", "for", "you", "to", "lead", "a", "sort", "of", "healthy", ",", "active", "life", "given", "that", "you", "came", "from", "two", "parents", "who", "were", "both", "alcoholics", ",", "were", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "EX", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Did that sort of send you the message right, I was not going to abuse myself that way?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "that", "sort", "of", "send", "you", "the", "message", "right", ",", "I", "was", "not", "going", "to", "abuse", "myself", "that", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "No, I never made up my mind -- I never said that to myself, I just wasn't that interested in, you know -- and I always felt there was something that was going to happen.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "never", "made", "up", "my", "mind", "--", "I", "never", "said", "that", "to", "myself", ",", "I", "just", "was", "n't", "that", "interested", "in", ",", "you", "know", "--", "and", "I", "always", "felt", "there", "was", "something", "that", "was", "going", "to", "happen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "Is that what it was?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "it", "was", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "We didn't have the money.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "did", "n't", "have", "the", "money", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["UCLA"]}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "And without that, it would never have happened?", "question_tokens": ["And", "without", "that", ",", "it", "would", "never", "have", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "Well, not -- you know, I don't know what would've happened, but that was when I was bitten by the theatrical bug at UCLA.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "not", "--", "you", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "would", "'ve", "happened", ",", "but", "that", "was", "when", "I", "was", "bitten", "by", "the", "theatrical", "bug", "at", "UCLA", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "But this was a guy who hired you and a group to come perform, right?", "question_tokens": ["But", "this", "was", "a", "guy", "who", "hired", "you", "and", "a", "group", "to", "come", "perform", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "Perform at a black-tie dinner party.", "answer_tokens": ["Perform", "at", "a", "black-tie", "dinner", "party", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "And he didn't want you to ever say who he was?", "question_tokens": ["And", "he", "did", "n't", "want", "you", "to", "ever", "say", "who", "he", "was", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "Correct.", "answer_tokens": ["Correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "And you never have, right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "never", "have", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "And you did all those things, didn't you?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "did", "all", "those", "things", ",", "did", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "But you've met up with this guy, didn't you?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "'ve", "met", "up", "with", "this", "guy", ",", "did", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "Do you think if you live a dream properly and you have this game plan luck comes your way?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "if", "you", "live", "a", "dream", "properly", "and", "you", "have", "this", "game", "plan", "luck", "comes", "your", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "You have to be ready.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "have", "to", "be", "ready", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "You really don't think so?", "question_tokens": ["You", "really", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "URNETT: No, I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["URNETT", ":", "No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "Doesn't that create even more competition?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "n't", "that", "create", "even", "more", "competition", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "VB", "RB", "RBR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "No, we worked very well together.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "we", "worked", "very", "well", "together", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "Rivals and all that?", "question_tokens": ["Rivals", "and", "all", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "No, no, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "And when you -- when you met him, he had eight children already?", "question_tokens": ["And", "when", "you", "--", "when", "you", "met", "him", ",", "he", "had", "eight", "children", "already", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "And you then had three more children?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "then", "had", "three", "more", "children", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "CD", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "So it's now eleven?", "question_tokens": ["So", "it", "'s", "now", "eleven", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "And why didn't it work out, the marriage, do you think, when you look back on it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "why", "did", "n't", "it", "work", "out", ",", "the", "marriage", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "when", "you", "look", "back", "on", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "RP", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "Well, I think towards the end, I -- it's really too personal, but we also parted as friends.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "towards", "the", "end", ",", "I", "--", "it", "'s", "really", "too", "personal", ",", "but", "we", "also", "parted", "as", "friends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "ORGAN: He's 20 years younger than you, yes?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "He", "'s", "20", "years", "younger", "than", "you", ",", "yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "It's not bad, is it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "bad", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "Not bad at all.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "bad", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "What have you learned about who you need to be around?", "question_tokens": ["What", "have", "you", "learned", "about", "who", "you", "need", "to", "be", "around", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "That's an interesting question.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "an", "interesting", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "Is that an integral part of your life?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "an", "integral", "part", "of", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "I mean as you get older, do you get more selfish?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "as", "you", "get", "older", ",", "do", "you", "get", "more", "selfish", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "I don't have any boring friends.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "have", "any", "boring", "friends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "They're too emotionally needy?", "question_tokens": ["They", "'re", "too", "emotionally", "needy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "The drama queens?", "question_tokens": ["The", "drama", "queens", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "But you've learned the power of saying no?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "'ve", "learned", "the", "power", "of", "saying", "no", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "And is there something you have to learn with time, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["And", "is", "there", "something", "you", "have", "to", "learn", "with", "time", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "Do you feel real love from them or not?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "real", "love", "from", "them", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "I -- yes, I felt love from them.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "yes", ",", "I", "felt", "love", "from", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Did she really?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "she", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "URNETT: Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["URNETT", ":", "Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "Well, that's just great, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "just", "great", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "Love it.", "answer_tokens": ["Love", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "Why should it always be the older guy with a younger woman?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "should", "it", "always", "be", "the", "older", "guy", "with", "a", "younger", "woman", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "Exactly, exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", ",", "exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "But when you look back, you've never felt that fame itself has had any kind of corrosive impact on your life?", "question_tokens": ["But", "when", "you", "look", "back", ",", "you", "'ve", "never", "felt", "that", "fame", "itself", "has", "had", "any", "kind", "of", "corrosive", "impact", "on", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "No, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "That wasn't like it in your day, was it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "was", "n't", "like", "it", "in", "your", "day", ",", "was", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "URNETT: No, also I'm not -- I don't think even if I were around today and this was my time to be on television, I don't think I would be pursued as much.", "answer_tokens": ["URNETT", ":", "No", ",", "also", "I", "'m", "not", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "even", "if", "I", "were", "around", "today", "and", "this", "was", "my", "time", "to", "be", "on", "television", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "I", "would", "be", "pursued", "as", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "Can you relate to that?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "relate", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "What was the trick, you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "trick", ",", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "The trick was I got her into rehab before she was going to turn 18.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "trick", "was", "I", "got", "her", "into", "rehab", "before", "she", "was", "going", "to", "turn", "18", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "Is it harder when you've got somebody like Charlie who's 50 now?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "harder", "when", "you", "'ve", "got", "somebody", "like", "Charlie", "who", "'s", "50", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "WP", "POS", "CD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "That's harder.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "harder", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "It's not supposed to be that way, is it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "supposed", "to", "be", "that", "way", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "No, it's not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "Or do you live with it every day?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "do", "you", "live", "with", "it", "every", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "I live with it every day.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "live", "with", "it", "every", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "Did you feel that, devastating though it was that she died in her late 30s, that actually because of the way she turned her life around in her teens, you kind of got possibly 20 more years than you may have done, had she continued down the early route?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "feel", "that", ",", "devastating", "though", "it", "was", "that", "she", "died", "in", "her", "late", "30s", ",", "that", "actually", "because", "of", "the", "way", "she", "turned", "her", "life", "around", "in", "her", "teens", ",", "you", "kind", "of", "got", "possibly", "20", "more", "years", "than", "you", "may", "have", "done", ",", "had", "she", "continued", "down", "the", "early", "route", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "CD", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "CD", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "Totally.", "answer_tokens": ["Totally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "Did you change your outlook on life?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "change", "your", "outlook", "on", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "I think I have the same outlook I had before.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "have", "the", "same", "outlook", "I", "had", "before", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "And how are you finding that?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "are", "you", "finding", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "I'm doing OK.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "doing", "OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "What kind of book is it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "book", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "I don't want to say yet.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "say", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "They didn't really want to do it?", "question_tokens": ["They", "did", "n't", "really", "want", "to", "do", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "They didn't want to do it and they didn't think we'd run past even a half a season.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "did", "n't", "want", "to", "do", "it", "and", "they", "did", "n't", "think", "we", "'d", "run", "past", "even", "a", "half", "a", "season", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "This was going to be big?", "question_tokens": ["This", "was", "going", "to", "be", "big", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "When they renewed us.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "they", "renewed", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "Was it controlled chaos?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "controlled", "chaos", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "Yes, it was.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "Did he have it done?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "have", "it", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "No, he said his wife's sister has a weak chin and he wanted to know what I went through.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "he", "said", "his", "wife", "'s", "sister", "has", "a", "weak", "chin", "and", "he", "wanted", "to", "know", "what", "I", "went", "through", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 644, "question": "Your weak bladder cost you possibly another three hours of Marlon Brando?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "weak", "bladder", "cost", "you", "possibly", "another", "three", "hours", "of", "Marlon", "Brando", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 645, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marlon Brando"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 663, "question": "Was that fun for you?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "fun", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 664, "answer": "Oh yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 680, "question": "Who were the greatest stars of them all?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "were", "the", "greatest", "stars", "of", "them", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "That's --", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 690, "question": "Are you really?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 691, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 692, "question": "How is her voice these days?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "her", "voice", "these", "days", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 693, "answer": "It's pretty good, actually.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "pretty", "good", ",", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 705, "question": "Did you?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 706, "answer": "Oh, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 707, "question": "I mean, what is not to love?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "what", "is", "not", "to", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 708, "answer": "They've both quite rugged chaps.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'ve", "both", "quite", "rugged", "chaps", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 714, "question": "But have you always tried to surround yourself with funny people too?", "question_tokens": ["But", "have", "you", "always", "tried", "to", "surround", "yourself", "with", "funny", "people", "too", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 715, "answer": "I don't try to, but I'm lucky to have them around.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "try", "to", ",", "but", "I", "'m", "lucky", "to", "have", "them", "around", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 727, "question": "Is it a particular genius, that, to be a great gag merchant?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "a", "particular", "genius", ",", "that", ",", "to", "be", "a", "great", "gag", "merchant", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 728, "answer": "Oh, I think.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "think", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 741, "question": "I want you to tell me, what's the moment you would relive if you had the chance?", "question_tokens": ["I", "want", "you", "to", "tell", "me", ",", "what", "'s", "the", "moment", "you", "would", "relive", "if", "you", "had", "the", "chance", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 742, "answer": "URNETT: I think it was probably when I lost out on a show that I was auditioning for.", "answer_tokens": ["URNETT", ":", "I", "think", "it", "was", "probably", "when", "I", "lost", "out", "on", "a", "show", "that", "I", "was", "auditioning", "for", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 759, "question": "Can you still do it?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "still", "do", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 760, "answer": "I'll try.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "try", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 786, "question": "Is that in the pipeline?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "in", "the", "pipeline", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 787, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]